Guide to the Student Agencies records, 1901-1990.
Student Agencies records, 1901-1990
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Student Agencies records, 1901-1990.
37-7-655
Student Agencies, Inc. (Ithaca, N.Y.)
10.6 cubic ft.
Photographs, financial records, board minutes, training manuals, employee profiles, old advertisements, a scrapbook, correspondence, newsclippings, and other records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs, financial records, board minutes, training manuals, employee profiles, old advertisements, and other records of Student Agencies, Inc., Student Agencies Properties, Inc., and Student Agencies Foundation. Also, scrapbook of papers relating mainly to the laundry agency, as well as other documents.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Student Agencies were student owned and operated businesses which provided part-time employment for Cornell University students. Included were a laundry agency, established in 1896, a room agency, and a periodical agency
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs, financial records, board minutes, training manuals, employee profiles, old advertisements, and other records of Student Agencies, Inc., Student Agencies Properties, Inc., and Student Agencies Foundation. Also, scrapbook of papers, compiled mainly by Donald Ellis Huntington, relating mainly to the laundry agency, but also to the room and periodical agencies; included are correspondence, financial records, rental agreements and other legal documents, information regarding operations, policy, and student competition for position, and newspaper clippings. Also, broadsides and publications, 1988-1990, including Entrepreneurfest, March 1990. Includes one volume of articles of confederation and directors' meetings minutes, 1908-1917.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Student Agencies, inc. (Ithaca, N.Y.); Huntington, Donald Ellis.; Cornell University--Students.; Student Agencies Foundation (Ithaca, N.Y.); Student Agencies Properties, inc. (Ithaca, N.Y.)
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.)--Commerce.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Scrapbook, ca. 1901-1920 (Box 1)
- Old Pictures of Student Agencies, Inc., and Misc. (Box 2)
- 1967-1971: financial statements, board minutes, and misc. (Box 3)
- 1957-1965: financial statements, board minutes, and misc. (Box 4)
- 1971-1975: financial statements, board minutes, and misc. (Box 5)
- 1910-1941: financial statements, board minutes, training manuals and misc. (Box 6)
- Statement of purpose, employee profiles, minutes of Student Agencies, Inc., Student Agencies Properties, Inc., and Student Agencies Foundation (Box 7)
- 1976-1979: financial statements, board minutes, and misc. (Box 8)
- 1943-1954: financial statements, board minutes, and misc. (Box 9)
- Laundry service ledgers, accounting records, financial statements (Box 10)
- Corporate budgets and old advertisements (Box 11)
- Broadsides and publications (Box 12)
- Volume, articles, minutes (Box 13)